Christian Provido Front-end Web Developer Personal Info Address Moonwalk Subd. Talon 5 Las-Pinas City, Metro Manila, PH Skype and Slack E-mail WWW LinkedIn Github Soft Skills Communication Advanced Collaboration Advanced Hard skills GIMP/Photoshop Advanced HTML/CSS Advanced

JavaScript

Accomplished front-end and email developer motivated by challenging projects and fresh ideas. Extensive experience designing & building websites (using HTML5, CSS3 and various web scripting technologies) as well as responsive emails compatible in over 30+ email clients.

Experience

2021-09 -Present

- Developing of responsive HTML emails from Adobe Photoshop and XD Files
- Setup campaigns in Adobe Campaign Classic
- Creating technical and campaign workflows using JavaScript in ACC
- During my free time, I create custom tools for email development using Nodejs and JavaScript

2019-05 -2021-05

ITMishelle

MRM

- Freelance Front End Developer support on contract basis
- Coordinating with Japanese clients and various small businesses to finalize designs and confirm requirements
- Creating custom mockups and developing intuitive UIs and Designing responsive webpages with accessibility standards in mind
- Testing frontend code in multiple browsers to ensure cross-browser compatibility

2018-01 -2021-08

The Defence Works

- Customise responsive cross-browser compatible landing pages using HTML(5), CSS(3), JS and jQuery
- Optimise & hand coded 90% of training emails and newsletters for custom events compatible in over 30+ email clients
- · Test and troubleshoot HTML emails using Litmus.
- Worked as a Virtual Assistant and Lead Generation Specialist

Education

2013-01 -2013-02

- Tekguru

• Training Comptia A+ Essentials 2009 Objectives with Practical Application

2002 -2008

Intermediate

AMA College of Las Pinas

- Followed my passion developing websites and script pages
- Excelled in user experience and user interface work

Interest

Playing Boardgames, Mountain Biking, Studying and learning new web development technologies, Playing video games